eliademy.com 2015-03-18

# Eliademy | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Effective on February 11th 2013 

CBTec Ltd (owner of the Eliademy.com) is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy describes how our service Eliademy.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on application and by using our service.

CBTec Ltd will never use your personal information in order to sell advertisements.

CBTec Ltd will never use your course content in any other purpose or claims any copyright on your content. The content that you include into the service is yours. 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Your email address (that you use upon registration)
  * Your full name (that you use upon registration)
  * We do not validate by any means if the names used upon registration belong to an actual person
  * We store information related to pictures used in your user profile section but we do not analyze those 
  * We store information in our servers related to the content of your course but that information belongs to you and we do not claim any copyright over the information stored in our servers

We collect this information when you: 

  * Set up an account

We use this information only to create your account and provide the service. 

### Information Sharing

We will NOT share your personal information with third parties. We do NOT sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with third parties.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or legal process served on our website) and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. 

### Tracking Technologies

As is true of most websites & services, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or page views. 

We use this information, which does not usually identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole and improve the service performance.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Eliademy.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by by emailing our Customer Support at [info@cloudberrytec.com](mailto:info@cloudberrytec.com)

Our website offers blogs or community forums to allow you to learn more about us. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information you choose to submit in blogs, forums, chat areas, instant message services, bulletin boards, or any other publicly accessible service or website. 

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us [info@cloudberrytec.com](mailto:info@cloudberrytec.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [info@cloudberrytec.com](mailto:info@cloudberrytec.com)

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update privacy policy and register from time to time as our information practices are modified or changed. If we make any material changes to this policy that affect your personal information, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
